Privacy Policy for Obasu Icons Pack

Effective Date: January 1, 2024

1. Introduction

Welcome to Obasu Icons Pack. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and protect your information when you use our app. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. By accessing or using our app, you consent to the practices described in this policy.

2. Information We Collect

To provide you with a seamless and enhanced user experience, we may collect and use the following types of information:

2.1. Device Information
We collect non-personally identifiable information about your device, including device brand, model, and screen dimensions. This information helps us design and optimize icons that are compatible with various devices. It is important to note that this data is used solely for improving the app's functionality and is not linked to you personally.

2.2. App Usage Data
We may collect information on how you interact with the app, including features used and time spent on the app. This data helps us understand user behavior and improve the app's performance and usability.

3. Permissions and Their Usage

To offer a full range of features and functionalities, our app requires the following permissions:

3.1. Storage Permissions

Read the Contents of Your Shared Storage: This permission allows the app to access files on your device's storage, enabling us to manage and store wallpapers and other related assets.
Modify System Settings: This permission is necessary for the app to set and adjust wallpapers and other system settings on your device.
3.2. Network and Connectivity Permissions

Have Full Network Access: Enables the app to access the internet to fetch updates, content, and other relevant information.
View Network Connections: Allows us to monitor network connections to optimize the app's performance.
View Wi-Fi Connections: Provides insight into the type of network connection for improving app functionality and performance.
3.3. System and Device Permissions

Set Wallpaper: Grants the app permission to set and change wallpapers on your device.
Adjust Your Wallpaper Size: Allows the app to resize wallpapers to ensure they fit your screen properly.
Prevent Phone from Sleeping: Ensures the app can continue running and delivering notifications even when the device screen is off.
Run at Startup: Enables the app to start automatically when your device is powered on.
Control Vibration: Manages vibration settings for notifications and alerts within the app.
Show Notifications: Allows the app to display notifications for updates, reminders, and other relevant information.
Run Foreground Service: Permits the app to run services in the foreground, maintaining performance and responsiveness.
4. Use of Information

The information we collect is used for the following purposes:

Enhancing User Experience: Device information and app usage data help us design better icons and improve app features based on user feedback and behavior.
App Functionality: Permissions such as setting wallpapers and adjusting wallpaper size are essential for the core functionalities of the app.
Service Improvements: Usage data and feedback help us identify areas for improvement and ensure that the app meets your needs and expectations.
5. Data Security

We are committed to protecting your information. We use industry-standard security measures to safeguard your data against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction. However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet or electronic storage is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee absolute security.

6. Third-Party Services

Our app may contain links to third-party services and websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third-party services you interact with to understand their data collection and use practices.

7. Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our practices or for other operational, legal, or regulatory reasons. We will notify you of any significant changes by posting the revised policy on this page with an updated effective date. We encourage you to review this policy periodically to stay informed about how we are protecting your information.

8. Your Rights and Choices

You have the right to access, update, or delete your information. If you wish to exercise these rights or have any concerns about how your information is handled, please contact us using the information provided below.

9. Contact Us

If you have any questions, concerns, or requests related to this Privacy Policy or your personal information, please contact us at:

Obasu Icons Pack
Email: samneill852@gmail.com