English Version:
Privacy Policy for Obasu Icons Pack
Developer: Tasneem Abbas
Effective Date: January 1, 2024

This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures on the collection, use, and disclosure of your information when you use the Obasu Icons Pack ("Application") and informs you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you. By using the Application, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

1. Introduction

Obasu Icons Pack ("we," "us," or "our") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines what information we collect, how we use it, and how we safeguard it. It applies to all users of the Application, which includes all software programs and services provided by the Company.

2. Definitions

Account: A unique account created for you to access the Application or parts of the Application.
Application: The software program provided by the Company, named "Obasu Icons Pack," downloaded by you on any electronic device.
Company: Refers to Obasu Icons Pack.
Country: Refers to the country in which the Company is located.
Cookies: Small files placed on your device containing browsing history details.
Device: Any electronic device capable of accessing the Application, such as a mobile phone, tablet, or computer.
Personal Data: Any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.
Service: Refers to the Application and its features.
Service Provider: A third party that processes data on behalf of the Company to facilitate the Service.
Usage Data: Data collected automatically through the Application or Service infrastructure (e.g., time spent using the Application).
You: The individual using the Application, or the company/legal entity on behalf of which such individual is using the Application.
3. Information We Collect

3.1. Personal Data
While using our Application, we may request certain personally identifiable information to identify or contact you, which may include but is not limited to:

Email address
First name and last name
Usage Data
3.2. Usage Data
We collect Usage Data automatically when you use the Application. This may include information such as your Device's Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of the Application you visit, and the time and date of your visit. When you access the Application via a mobile device, we may collect information such as the type of mobile device, unique device ID, IP address, mobile operating system, and type of mobile internet browser.

3.3. Information Collected While Using the Application
To provide and enhance features of our Application, we may request access to certain information on your device, with your prior permission:

Storage Access: Read the contents of your shared storage and modify system settings to set and store wallpapers.
Location Information: To customize services, if needed.
Network Access: Full network access to check for updates and interact with server-side services.
Other Device Information: Device brand, screen dimensions, and system settings to optimize the icons pack.
4. Use of Your Personal Data

The Company may use Personal Data for the following purposes:

To Provide and Maintain the Service: Monitor the usage and ensure optimal performance.
Manage Your Account: Allow registration and access to various functionalities of the Application.
Contact You: Notify you via email, SMS, or other forms of electronic communication regarding updates, changes, or promotional offers.
Improve the Service: To enhance and customize the Application, including storing and adjusting wallpapers.
Business Transfers: To consider or execute mergers, acquisitions, or asset sales involving the Application.
Other Purposes: Data analysis, usage trend identification, promotional campaign effectiveness evaluation, and overall improvement of the Application.
5. Sharing Your Personal Data

We may share your information in the following situations:

With Service Providers: For monitoring and analyzing Application use and providing specific functionalities.
For Business Transfers: In connection with mergers, acquisitions, or sales of assets.
With Affiliates: To enhance our services and promotional activities.
With Business Partners: For joint promotions, products, and services.
With Other Users: When you voluntarily share information in public areas.
With Your Consent: For any other purpose upon obtaining your explicit consent.
6. Retention of Your Personal Data

The Company will retain your Personal Data only for as long as necessary for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy. Usage Data will generally be retained for a shorter period, except where used to strengthen security or improve functionality.

7. Transfer of Your Personal Data

Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside your jurisdiction, where data protection laws may differ. By submitting your information, you agree to this transfer. We ensure that your data is treated securely with appropriate safeguards in place.

8. Disclosure of Your Personal Data

We may disclose your Personal Data:

To comply with legal obligations.
To protect and defend the Company’s rights or property.
To prevent or investigate wrongdoing related to the Application.
For protecting the safety of users or the public.
9. Data Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect your data. However, no internet transmission method or electronic storage is 100% secure. We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your data but cannot guarantee absolute security.

10. Children’s Privacy

Our Application does not target individuals under the age of 13. If we become aware of data collected from a child without parental consent, we take steps to remove that data from our servers.

11. Permissions Overview

To provide an enhanced user experience, our Application requires the following permissions:

Read/Write Storage: To access and manage wallpapers and icons.
Modify System Settings: To set wallpapers and adjust display settings.
Full Network Access: For updates, content downloads, and service interactions.
View Network/Wi-Fi Connections: To optimize Application performance based on network availability.
Set Wallpaper and Adjust Size: To provide wallpaper-related functionalities.
Run at Startup: To maintain Application settings upon device restart.
Control Vibration: For notifications.
Prevent Phone from Sleeping: To ensure proper functioning of the Application.
Run Foreground Service: To maintain active Application services.
12. Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy periodically. We will notify you of changes via email or a prominent notice within the Application, updating the "Effective Date" accordingly.

13. Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Obasu Icons Pack
Email: samneill852@gmail.com
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Chinese Version:
隐私政策 - Obasu 图标包
开发者: 塔斯尼姆·阿巴斯 (Tasneem Abbas)
生效日期: 2024年1月1日

本隐私政策介绍了您在使用 Obasu Icons Pack ("应用程序") 时我们收集、使用和披露您的信息的政策和程序，并告知您有关您的隐私权以及法律如何保护您的权利。通过使用应用程序，您同意按照本政策收集和使用信息。

简介
Obasu Icons Pack ("我们", "我们的") 致力于保护您的隐私。本隐私政策概述了我们收集的信息、使用信息的方式以及我们如何保护信息。它适用于所有使用该应用程序的用户，包括公司提供的所有软件程序和服务。

定义
账户：为您创建的用于访问应用程序或部分应用程序的唯一账户。
应用程序：公司提供的软件程序，名为“Obasu Icons Pack”，您在任何电子设备上下载使用。
公司：指 Obasu Icons Pack。
国家：指公司所在的国家。
Cookie：存储在您设备上的包含浏览历史的小文件。
设备：任何能够访问应用程序的电子设备，例如手机、平板电脑或计算机。
个人数据：指任何与已识别或可识别个人相关的信息。
服务：指应用程序及其功能。
服务提供商：代表公司处理数据的第三方，用于促进服务。
使用数据：通过应用程序或服务基础设施自动收集的数据（例如，使用应用程序的时间）。
您：使用应用程序的个人，或代表其使用应用程序的公司/法律实体。

我们收集的信息
3.1. 个人数据
在使用我们的应用程序时，我们可能会要求您提供某些个人身份信息，以识别或联系您，这可能包括但不限于：

电子邮件地址
名字和姓氏
使用数据

3.2. 使用数据
我们会在您使用应用程序时自动收集使用数据。这可能包括您的设备的互联网协议 (IP) 地址、浏览器类型、浏览器版本、您访问的应用程序页面、访问的时间和日期等信息。当您通过移动设备访问应用程序时，我们可能会收集诸如移动设备类型、唯一设备 ID、IP 地址、移动操作系统等信息。

3.3. 使用应用程序时收集的信息
为了提供和增强应用程序的功能，我们可能会在获得您的许可后请求访问您设备上的某些信息：

存储访问：读取共享存储的内容，并修改系统设置以设置和存储壁纸。
位置信息：如果需要，定制服务。
网络访问：完全网络访问，用于检查更新和与服务器交互。
其他设备信息：设备品牌、屏幕尺寸和系统设置，以优化图标包。

我们如何使用您的个人数据
公司可能会将个人数据用于以下目的：

提供和维护服务：监控使用情况并确保最佳性能。
管理您的账户：允许注册并访问应用程序的各项功能。
与您联系：通过电子邮件、短信或其他形式的电子通讯通知您更新、更改或促销活动。
改进服务：增强和定制应用程序，包括存储和调整壁纸。
业务转让：考虑或执行与应用程序相关的合并、收购或资产销售。
其他用途：数据分析、识别使用趋势、评估促销活动的有效性以及应用程序的整体改进。

共享您的个人数据
我们可能在以下情况下共享您的信息：

与服务提供商：用于监控和分析应用程序的使用情况以及提供特定功能。
业务转让：与合并、收购或资产出售有关的情况。
与关联公司：增强我们的服务和促销活动。
与商业伙伴：用于联合促销、产品和服务。
与其他用户：当您自愿在公共区域分享信息时。
经您同意：为任何其他目的获取您的明确同意。

您个人数据的保留
公司将仅保留您的个人数据以实现本隐私政策中规定的目的。使用数据一般保留时间较短，除非用于加强安全性或提高功能。

您个人数据的转移
您的信息可能会传输到并存储在您所在辖区以外的计算机上，数据保护法律可能有所不同。提交您的信息即表示您同意此类传输。我们确保您的数据得到安全处理，并采取了适当的安全措施。

您个人数据的披露
我们可能会披露您的个人数据：

为遵守法律义务。
为保护公司权益或财产。
为防止或调查与应用程序有关的不当行为。
为保护用户或公众的安全。

数据安全
我们采取适当的安全措施保护您的数据。然而，任何通过互联网传输或电子存储的方法都不是100%安全的。我们努力使用商业上可接受的手段保护您的数据，但不能保证绝对安全。

儿童隐私
我们的应用程序不面向13岁以下的个人。如果我们发现未经父母同意收集了儿童数据，我们将采取步骤将这些数据从服务器中删除。

权限概述
为了提供更好的用户体验，我们的应用程序需要以下权限：

读取/写入存储：访问和管理壁纸及图标。
修改系统设置：设置壁纸并调整显示设置。
完全网络访问：用于更新、内容下载和服务交互。
查看网络/Wi-Fi 连接：根据网络可用性优化应用程序性能。
设置壁纸并调整大小：提供与壁纸相关的功能。
启动时运行：在设备重启后保持应用程序设置。
控制震动：用于通知。
防止设备进入睡眠模式：确保应用程序正常运行。
前台服务：保持应用程序服务的活动状态。

本隐私政策的变更
我们可能会定期更新我们的隐私政策。我们将通过电子邮件或应用程序内显著通知您，并相应更新“生效日期”。

联系我们
如果您对本隐私政策有任何疑问或顾虑，请通过以下方式联系我们：

Obasu Icons Pack
电子邮件：samneill852@gmail.com
