Privacy Policy for Obasu Icons Pack
Effective Date: January 1, 2024

This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures on the collection, use, and disclosure of your information when you use the Obasu Icons Pack ("Application") and informs you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you. By using the Application, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

1. Introduction

Obasu Icons Pack ("we," "us," or "our") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines what information we collect, how we use it, and how we safeguard it. It applies to all users of the Application, which includes all software programs and services provided by the Company.

2. Definitions

Account: A unique account created for you to access the Application or parts of the Application.
Application: The software program provided by the Company, named "Obasu Icons Pack," downloaded by you on any electronic device.
Company: Refers to Obasu Icons Pack.
Country: Refers to the country in which the Company is located.
Cookies: Small files placed on your device containing browsing history details.
Device: Any electronic device capable of accessing the Application, such as a mobile phone, tablet, or computer.
Personal Data: Any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.
Service: Refers to the Application and its features.
Service Provider: A third party that processes data on behalf of the Company to facilitate the Service.
Usage Data: Data collected automatically through the Application or Service infrastructure (e.g., time spent using the Application).
You: The individual using the Application, or the company/legal entity on behalf of which such individual is using the Application.
3. Information We Collect

3.1. Personal Data
While using our Application, we may request certain personally identifiable information to identify or contact you, which may include but is not limited to:

Email address
First name and last name
Usage Data
3.2. Usage Data
We collect Usage Data automatically when you use the Application. This may include information such as your Device's Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of the Application you visit, and the time and date of your visit. When you access the Application via a mobile device, we may collect information such as the type of mobile device, unique device ID, IP address, mobile operating system, and type of mobile internet browser.

3.3. Information Collected While Using the Application
To provide and enhance features of our Application, we may request access to certain information on your device, with your prior permission:

Storage Access: Read the contents of your shared storage and modify system settings to set and store wallpapers.
Location Information: To customize services, if needed.
Network Access: Full network access to check for updates and interact with server-side services.
Other Device Information: Device brand, screen dimensions, and system settings to optimize the icons pack.
4. Use of Your Personal Data

The Company may use Personal Data for the following purposes:

To Provide and Maintain the Service: Monitor the usage and ensure optimal performance.
Manage Your Account: Allow registration and access to various functionalities of the Application.
Contact You: Notify you via email, SMS, or other forms of electronic communication regarding updates, changes, or promotional offers.
Improve the Service: To enhance and customize the Application, including storing and adjusting wallpapers.
Business Transfers: To consider or execute mergers, acquisitions, or asset sales involving the Application.
Other Purposes: Data analysis, usage trend identification, promotional campaign effectiveness evaluation, and overall improvement of the Application.
5. Sharing Your Personal Data

We may share your information in the following situations:

With Service Providers: For monitoring and analyzing Application use and providing specific functionalities.
For Business Transfers: In connection with mergers, acquisitions, or sales of assets.
With Affiliates: To enhance our services and promotional activities.
With Business Partners: For joint promotions, products, and services.
With Other Users: When you voluntarily share information in public areas.
With Your Consent: For any other purpose upon obtaining your explicit consent.
6. Retention of Your Personal Data

The Company will retain your Personal Data only for as long as necessary for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy. Usage Data will generally be retained for a shorter period, except where used to strengthen security or improve functionality.

7. Transfer of Your Personal Data

Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside your jurisdiction, where data protection laws may differ. By submitting your information, you agree to this transfer. We ensure that your data is treated securely with appropriate safeguards in place.

8. Disclosure of Your Personal Data

We may disclose your Personal Data:

To comply with legal obligations.
To protect and defend the Company’s rights or property.
To prevent or investigate wrongdoing related to the Application.
For protecting the safety of users or the public.
9. Data Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect your data. However, no internet transmission method or electronic storage is 100% secure. We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your data but cannot guarantee absolute security.

10. Children’s Privacy

Our Application does not target individuals under the age of 13. If we become aware of data collected from a child without parental consent, we take steps to remove that data from our servers.

11. Permissions Overview

To provide an enhanced user experience, our Application requires the following permissions:

Read/Write Storage: To access and manage wallpapers and icons.
Modify System Settings: To set wallpapers and adjust display settings.
Full Network Access: For updates, content downloads, and service interactions.
View Network/Wi-Fi Connections: To optimize Application performance based on network availability.
Set Wallpaper and Adjust Size: To provide wallpaper-related functionalities.
Run at Startup: To maintain Application settings upon device restart.
Control Vibration: For notifications.
Prevent Phone from Sleeping: To ensure proper functioning of the Application.
Run Foreground Service: To maintain active Application services.
12. Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy periodically. We will notify you of changes via email or a prominent notice within the Application, updating the "Effective Date" accordingly.

13. Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Obasu Icons Pack
Email: samneill852@gmail.com
